(Raj:)That was my last hope.
I'm gonna be deported.
Sent home in disgrace.
(Raj:)Exposed to the sardonic barbs
of my cousin Sanjay.
(Raj:)Or as you may know him,
Dave from AT&T Customer Service.
-I'm really gonna miss you.
-Will you come visit me in India?
(Howard:)Gee, that's like a 17-hour flight.
(Howard:)How about I meet you halfway?
(Raj:)Halfway is 600 miles
off the coast of Japan.
(Howard:)Tell you what, we'll Skype.
(Sheldon(arriving):)-Gentlemen.
-Hey.
(Sheldon:)Raj, did you get the job
with Professor Laughlin?
(Howard:)-No.
-I assumed as much, but never fear.
(Sheldon:)Like the subordinate male protagonist
in action movies who disappears...
...halfway through the second reel,
I have returned to save the day.
(Sheldon:)Odd. Usually he's met by cheers.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I was thinking about exploring
the string theory implications...